Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Lust and Lies=
=الشهوة والكذب=
Qingwan.
تشينغوان.
Have a safe journey home.
أتمنى لك رحلة آمنة إلى المنزل.
What a shame.
يا للعار.
Since your return,
منذ عودتك،
I haven't managed to treat you well.
لم أتمكن من معاملتك بشكل جيد.
Do you still remember it?
هل لازلت تتذكره؟
When we were small,
عندما كنا صغارا،
we made a pledge
لقد قطعنا عهدا
to visit so many places.
لزيارة العديد من الأماكن.
And I haven't taken you to any of them.
ولم آخذك إلى أي منهم.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
Tears
دموع
will make you look bad.
سيجعلك تبدو سيئا.
Huo Jin?
هوو جين؟
Huo Jin...
هوو جين...
Huo Jin!
هوو جين!
Is this the ending that you want?
هل هذه هي النهاية التي تريدها؟
You kidnapped me here
لقد اختطفتني هنا
to give yourself a way out, right?
لتمنح نفسك مخرجًا، أليس كذلك؟
Because you knew
لأنك عرفت
I'd protect you.
سأحميك.
And you knew I'd let the Huofeng Gang go
وعرفت أنني سأترك عصابة هووفينج تذهب
because of you.
بسببك.
You've manipulated me
لقد تلاعبت بي
using my love towards you.
استخدام حبي تجاهك.
You're free to use me too.
لك حرية استخدامي أيضاً.
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
♪Our first encounter left me in awe for a lifetime♪
♪لقد تركني لقاءنا الأول في حالة من الرهبة مدى الحياة♪
♪Feelings I can't shake off♪
♪مشاعر لا أستطيع التخلص منها♪
♪Quietly emerge♪
♪الظهور بهدوء♪
♪It was just a single glance♪
♪كانت مجرد نظرة واحدة♪
=Episode 17=
=الحلقة 17=
♪Sweet words exist only in dreams♪
♪الكلمات الحلوة موجودة فقط في الأحلام♪
♪Memories are like faded negatives♪
♪الذكريات مثل السلبيات الباهتة♪
♪Replaying endlessly♪
♪إعادة تشغيل بلا نهاية♪
I'm sorry, Father.
انا آسف يا أبي.
I failed to protect Jin.
لقد فشلت في حماية جين.
♪Amidst the light and shadow♪
♪وسط الضوء والظل♪
♪Love and hate blur together♪
♪الحب والكراهية يختلطان معًا♪
♪Why let ourselves fall deeper than we already are?♪
♪لماذا نسمح لأنفسنا بالسقوط بشكل أعمق مما نحن عليه بالفعل؟♪
♪Time can't outlast a heart that remembers♪
♪الوقت لا يمكن أن يدوم أكثر من القلب الذي يتذكر♪
♪The past has already found its peace♪
♪الماضي قد وجد سلامه بالفعل♪
♪You remain the same♪
♪أنت تبقى كما أنت♪
♪A longing I can never get over, like mist, like dreams♪
♪شوق لا يمكنني التغلب عليه أبدًا، مثل الضباب، مثل الأحلام♪
Jin.
إحساس.
Wake up.
استيقظ.
♪Amidst the light and shadow♪
♪وسط الضوء والظل♪
♪Love and hate blur together♪
♪الحب والكراهية يختلطان معًا♪
♪Why let ourselves fall deeper than we already are?♪
♪لماذا نسمح لأنفسنا بالسقوط بشكل أعمق مما نحن عليه بالفعل؟♪
♪Time can't outlast a heart that remembers♪
♪الوقت لا يمكن أن يدوم أكثر من القلب الذي يتذكر♪
♪The past has already found its peace♪
♪الماضي قد وجد سلامه بالفعل♪
♪You remain the same♪
♪أنت تبقى كما أنت♪
♪A longing I can never get over, like mist, like dreams♪
♪شوق لا يمكنني التغلب عليه أبدًا، مثل الضباب، مثل الأحلام♪
♪A moment apart feels like endless years♪
♪لحظة فراق تبدو وكأنها سنوات لا نهاية لها♪
♪Amidst the light and shadow♪
♪وسط الضوء والظل♪
♪Love and hate blur together♪
♪الحب والكراهية يختلطان معًا♪
♪Why let ourselves fall deeper than we already are?♪
♪لماذا نسمح لأنفسنا بالسقوط بشكل أعمق مما نحن عليه بالفعل؟♪
♪Time can't outlast a heart that remembers♪
♪الوقت لا يمكن أن يدوم أكثر من القلب الذي يتذكر♪
♪The past has already found its peace♪
♪الماضي قد وجد سلامه بالفعل♪
♪You remain the same♪
♪أنت تبقى كما أنت♪
♪A longing I can never get over, like mist, like dreams♪
♪شوق لا يمكنني التغلب عليه أبدًا، مثل الضباب، مثل الأحلام♪
What kind of girl likes such a stuff?
ما نوع الفتاة التي تحب مثل هذه الأشياء؟
We're one step closer to our vengeance.
نحن أقرب بخطوة واحدة إلى الانتقام.
Aren't you glad?
ألا أنت سعيد؟
But I've caused those innocent people's deaths.
ولكنني تسببت في وفاة هؤلاء الأبرياء.
Zhao Xun
تشاو شون
and the Ruan family.
وعائلة روان.
All of them were innocent too.
وكانوا جميعهم أبرياء أيضاً.
Living in this world,
العيش في هذا العالم،
we can't judge what is right and what is wrong.
لا يمكننا الحكم على ما هو الصواب وما هو الخطأ.
The only way
الطريقة الوحيدة
is an eye for an eye
العين بالعين
and a tooth
وسن
for a tooth.
للسن.
We shouldn't have treated Liu Yiyi this way.
لا ينبغي لنا أن نتعامل مع ليو ييي بهذه الطريقة.
At least she's sincere with you.
على الأقل أنها صادقة معك.
Well,
حسنًا،
all she cares about
كل ما يهمها
is my family property, no?
هل هي ملك عائلتي، أليس كذلك؟
There's nothing sincere about her.
لا يوجد شيء صادق فيها.
Could it be
هل يمكن أن يكون
that you and Huo Xiu are sincere with one another?
هل أنت و هوو شيو صادقان مع بعضكما البعض؟
Huo Jin is dead.
لقد مات هيو جين.
Huo Beishan has been postponing his burial
لقد أرجأ هوو بيشان دفنه
and insisted on having the banquet.
وأصر على إقامة المأدبة.
I can't help but find that fishy.
لا أستطيع إلا أن أجد هذا الأمر مريبًا.
What's there to be afraid of?
ما الذي يجب أن نخاف منه؟
That's our engagement party.
هذا حفل خطوبتنا.
We're the stars of the day.
نحن نجوم اليوم.
Have you been waiting here for long?
هل كنت تنتظر هنا لفترة طويلة؟
You and Sheng Weilian
أنت وشنغ ويليان
met there?
التقيت هناك؟
You seem to be all-knowing.
يبدو أنك تعرف كل شيء.
I know
أنا أعرف
more than you thought.
أكثر مما كنت تعتقد.
But I've chosen to be ignorant because of you.
ولكنني اخترت أن أكون جاهلاً بسببك.
But you've never believed me.
ولكنك لم تصدقني أبدًا.
That's because you're full of secrets,
هذا لأنك مليء بالأسرار،
and I can't figure you out.
ولا أستطيع أن أفهمك.
Don't stop me
لا توقفني
from doing what I want.
من القيام بما أريد.
Are you sure
هل أنت متأكد
Qingwan held the gun?
عقد تشينغوان البندقية؟
Uncle.
عم.
I swear.
أقسم.
She's had it all planned out.
لقد خططت لكل شيء.
I will kill you!
سأقتلك!
All the guests are almost here.
جميع الضيوف هنا تقريبا.
Hang in there.
إصمد.
Congratulations!
مبروك!
I have an announcement to make.
لدي إعلان أريد أن أقوله.
My daughter, Huo Qingwan,
ابنتي، هيو تشينغوان،
and the Sheng family will have a marriage alliance.
وسوف يكون لعائلة شنغ تحالف زواج.
An auspicious date will be picked for the wedding.
سيتم اختيار تاريخ مناسب لحفل الزفاف.
- Nice! - Great!
- لطيف! - عظيم!
Lovely!
محبوب!
Good!
جيد!
♪In a gentle night♪
♪في ليلة لطيفة♪
♪A bare face awaiting blush♪
♪وجه عارٍ ينتظر الاحمرار♪
♪Cups clink, voices overlap♪
♪أكواب تتصادم، أصوات متداخلة♪
♪We switch our roles♪
♪نحن نبدل الأدوار♪
♪Darkness fades, and daylight breaks♪
♪يتلاشى الظلام، ويشرق ضوء النهار♪
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
♪Do you remember the sound of the flute in the wind?♪
♪هل تتذكر صوت الناي في الريح؟♪
♪It whispers of the flame we shared♪
♪همس من اللهب الذي شاركناه♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪